<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<main>
	<!--Head should appear only once, and at the top-->
	<head title="Textview"/>
	<!--the rest can appear-->
	<title>SBTCVM Ternary Calculator help</title>
	<text>SBTCVM's Ternary calculator provides a specialized tool
for common Ternary Calculations.
</text>
	<img>calcsc.jpg</img>
	<text>
</text>
	<title>Input A:</title>
	<text>Input A is the primary input. 
</text>
	<title>Input B:</title>
	<text>Input B is the secondary input.
</text>
	
	<title>Inputs Explained:</title>
	<img>calcinput.png</img>
	<text>click on the decimal portion (D) to enter a decimal integer.
Click on the balanced ternary portion (T) to enter a balanced ternary integer.
When you enter a decimal or balanced ternary integer, you enter input mode.
cross conversion is preformed automatically when you leave input mode. (enter/left click)

When active, the inputs are highlighted in blue.

Note: if you want the result (RES) in one of the inputs, the "RES>A" and "RES>B"
buttons can be used.
</text>
	
	<title>Result and Status area:</title>
	<img>calcstat.png</img>
	<text>The result readouts look similar to the inputs, but you will see an
additional part labeled "s." This is the Status readout.
This will generally show information on Errors and
results of calculations.</text>
	<title>Buttons Explained:</title>
	<img>calcbtn.jpg</img>
	<text>"add":    add A and B
"sub":    subtract A and B
"div":    divide A by B
"mul":    multiply A by B
"copy A>B":    Copy A to B
"invert A":    Invert A "tritwise" (replace + with - and vice versa)
"mpi":    Calculate The Max positive integer of an integer (Decimal A) trits long.*
"mcv":    Calculate The Max combinations value of an integer (Decimal A) trits long.*
"res>A":    Copy Result to A **
"res>B":    Copy Result to B **
"copy B>A":    Copy B to A
"invert B":    Invert B "tritwise" (replace + with - and vice versa)
"mni":    Calculate The Max Negative integer of an integer (Decimal A) trits long.*
"swap":    Swap A with B
"help":    SBTCVM help
"quit":    quit the calculator.

*(limited to up to 36 due to technical and graphical limitations. you can use
the command shell equivalent if you wish to exceed 36)
**(these operations can be "locked" using shift+left click or right click.
In the case of "res>A" and "res>B", this triggers the operations after
every result-producing operation) these buttons will have a blue "light"
across the bottom (as shown in the image on the "res>A" button), when locked.

</text>

</main>