<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<main>
	<!--Head should appear only once, and at the top-->
	<head title="List Of programs"/>
	<!--the rest can appear-->
	<title>List Of programs. A quick reference:</title>
	<text>SBTCVM is distributed as an Application Suite
for working with Balanced Ternary on binary computers.
Here is a quick overview of what the various main programs are:
</text>
	<title>Command Line programs:</title>
	<div/>
	<text>MK2-CS.py : This is the SBTCVM command shell. It provides a handy CLI for working with the more technical tools.</text>
	<div/>
	<text>MK2-RUN.py : this is the command shell command "run". It starts SBTCVM with fine control. This is the same utility used by other utilities to launch the VM.</text>
	<div/>
	<text>MK2-GFX.py : This is a graphics conversion tool.</text>
	<div/>
	<text>MK2-GAT.py : SBTCVM Graphics Adapter Toolkit. This provides various helper functions related to SBTGA programming, such as generating framebuffer ranges from binary images (a PNG for example)</text>
	<div/>
	<text>MK2-TOOLS.py : This is a tools launcher/debugging tool. It's primarily used for testing, backend debugging, and wraps various backend functions as descrete programs.</text>
	<div/>
	<text>SBTCVM-asm2.py : This is SBTCVM's assembler. It's currently the best way to write SBTCVM programs, unless of course you like Machine code.
</text>
	<title>Special</title>
	<div/>
	<text>SBTCVM_MK2.py : This is the VM itself, though to run the VM, please use MK2-RUN.py or "run" in the command shell.</text>
	<lnk label="VM Overview">vmhelp.xml</lnk>
	<title>GUI programs.</title>
	<div/>
	<text>launcher.py : SBTCVM's Desktop multitasking environment and launcher.</text>
	<lnk label="SBTCVM Desktop">launcher.xml</lnk>
	<div/>
	<text>calc.py : A graphical Balanced Ternary Calculator, complete with simultanious decimal and balanced ternary representation, input in both base numbers, and automatic conversion among other features.</text>
	<lnk label="SBTCVM Calculator">calc.xml</lnk>
	<div/>
	<text>fileview2.py : SBTCVM's integrated file browser.</text>
	<lnk label="Fileview">fileview.xml</lnk>
	<div/>
	<text>settings.py : SBTCVM's Main Configuration Utility.</text>
	<lnk label="Settings">settings.xml</lnk>
	<div/>
	<text>theme.py : SBTCVM's Theme Configuration Utility.</text>
	<lnk label="Theme settings">theme.xml</lnk>
	<div/>
	<text>helpview.py : SBTCVM's Integrated Help system (this program) </text>
	<lnk label="Help on Help">helponhelp.xml</lnk>
</main>